http://www.misk.com/legal/privacy

Last Updated on: May 25, 2018
This Privacy Policy (Policy) governs the ways in which Misk.com, Inc. (Misk, we, us or our, including affiliates that controls, is controlled by, or is under common control with Misk) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from our customers, visitors to our websites, and visitors to our customer’s websites (Customers, you, or your).
In the course of providing Products to Customers or visitors to our website, we collect information.  The purpose of our Policy is to discuss how we handle the majority of information that we collect or which comes into our possession. Simply because information is discussed in this policy does not mean it is necessarily considered by us to be private or that it is legally protected. As used in this Policy, the term “Personal Data” means information relating to an individual who can be identified with reference to that information, either alone or in conjunction with other information. Our Policy supplements, but does not replace our Terms of Service and Acceptable Use Policy.  Those documents should be read in conjunction with this policy.  If at any time, you would like to know how specific information is handled, please email us at:  privacy@misk.com.
Because Misk is based in the United States and has customers worldwide, we also want to convey to you how we comply with applicable data protection laws (Data Protection Laws).  Processing Personal Data is necessary both to allow Misk to provide the Products under the Terms of Service and, with respect to domain name registration services, for legitimate interests pursued by Misk and other third parties. It may also be shared with our business partners or agents as provided in this Policy. If we decide to use the Personal Data for a purpose other than the purpose described in this Policy, we will provide you with prior notice and an opportunity to object to such processing.
Personal Data may reside or be transferred to a jurisdiction, such as the United States, other than the jurisdiction where you reside (your Home Jurisdiction). Misk takes data security very seriously, as described below and in our Terms of Service. You expressly consent to the transfer of Personal Data to a jurisdiction other than your Home Jurisdiction.
If we change our Policy, we will post an updated Policy to our website so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.
How we collect information
Cookies.  Our website uses cookies.  Cookies are small data files that are placed automatically on your computer by our computers or those of our third party service providers. Some of our business partners and equipment we use to provide products and services (Products) to you may also place cookies on your computer.  We do not control those cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.
Customer Information.  You provide us with your name, address, phone number, email address, username/password, credit/debit card or bank information and other Personal Data.  This information is mandatory. Company name (if applicable) and fax number may be provided on a voluntary basis. This information is provided in a number of ways:  registration, ordering, and other requests for information.  If you were referred to our site by a source known to us, this referral data is also recorded.  This information is all aggregated to create an administrative record that includes data related to the Products, how you use the Products, problems related to the Products, and notations from our staff about our relationship with you, among other things (Customer Information).
Domain Name Information.  When you register a domain name with us, we collect contact information such as name, address, phone number, email address, and other Personal Data, as well as specific information required by each top level domain name registry.  The specific information we collect during the registration process is set out in our Terms of Service (Domain Name Information). Domain Name Information may vary from registry to registry but is required.
Customer Inquiries.  If you contact us about a problem, or with a question, you may share specific information related to the reason you have contacted us (Customer Inquiry Information).  This information may be tied to, or input into, the Customer Information. You are not required to provide any specific Customer Inquiry Information; however, we may be unable to assist you if you do not provide specific information related to the subject of your contact.
Statistical Information.  All of our servers collect statistical information such as your IP address, date you visited, page you visited, computer you are using, and operating system, among other data (Statistical Information).
How We Use the Information We Collect
We process Personal Data pursuant to our legitimate interest in providing Products to you. This section describes how we use various categories of Personal Data, and whether we use it, or process it, in ways in which Misk, and our third party service providers, can identify you. This section also describes the specific purposes for which the Personal Data will be processed.
Cookies.  We use the information provided by the cookies to change the way our website looks to you; keep you logged in to certain areas of the website; enable the Products; ensure continued connection to our equipment; and to collect demographic data about where visitors to our website come from, go to, and how they behave.  Cookies may be used to identify you individually. If you do not wish to consent to the use of cookies, you should disable cookies in your browser. Consult the Help section of your browser for information relating to disabling cookies in your specific browser. However, if you disable cookies, Misk may not be able to provide Products to you.
Customer Information.  We use Customer Information to identify Customers individually.  Customer Information is used throughout our business to provide the Products to you and is required to enter into a contract with Misk for the purchase of our Products.  Personal Data related to payment, such as a Customer’s credit card number, is only used to ensure we receive payment for the Products.  It may be shared with third parties affiliated with us if they provide Products through us to you and those Products are billed by them independently.  No other Customer Information is disclosed outside Misk, except as provided below.
Domain Name Information.  All Domain Name Information is public information.  We only use this Domain Name Information to provide the Products.  When you sign up for domain registration Products, we share your Domain Name Information, as required by third parties to provide that service. This includes the applicable registry operator(s) and other third parties, such as the Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers (ICANN), escrow providers, law enforcement and others who may be entitled to receive the the Personal Data from the applicable registry operator(s). These third parties may use Domain Name Information differently. Providing Domain Name Information as described in the the Terms of Service is mandatory; if you do not provide the Domain Name Information, we will not be able to provide the requested Products, because we are contractually required to provide this information to registry operators and other third parties who make up the domain name system.
Customer Inquiries.  We use Customer Inquiry Information to identify you individually.  It is used throughout our business to provide the Products to you.  Customer Inquiry Information may be shared with third parties who help to identify and fix problems with the Products when we are not capable of doing so ourselves.
Statistical Information.  We use the Statistical Information to operate our hardware and software, diagnose problems and administer our website.  We may use this information to modify the Products based on who is visiting our website and what they are purchasing.  Statistical Information may be used to identify you individually. Third party service providers may also use web beacons to monitor or track this Statistical Information for us, and we may share Statistical Information with third-party service providers for similar purposes.
Emails From Misk.  While your account is active with us, you may not generally opt out of receiving Product related email communications from Misk such as order confirmation emails, critical Product changes/updates, new product notifications, etc.
Agents. We use credit card processing companies to bill you for the Products. We provide Customer Information to credit card processing companies.  These companies do not use Customer Information, or other personally identifiable information for any other purposes.
Other Disclosures.  Misk is required to comply with relevant laws, regulations, court/judicial orders, or legal process served.  Personal Data, as well as other categories of information covered by this Policy, may be disclosed to third parties if we determine, in our sole discretion, that such a disclosure is necessary or required.  We may also disclose this information if, in our sole discretion, such a disclosure is necessary or required to protect our interests or the interests of our customers, in connection with the sale of our business, and to contractors, and other third parties we use to help us create and operate the Products.
Data Security and Retention
The security of your Personal Data is important to us.  When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).  The information set out in this Policy is protected using industry standard security measures.  However, no means of communication or information transmission or storage is totally secure.  We are not responsible for loss corruption or unauthorized acquisition and use of information, or for any damages resulting therefrom, including unauthorized acquisition and use.  Please review our TOS for more information about data security.
We may retain and store Customer Information, Domain Name Information, Customer Inquiry Information and Statistical Information following termination of the Products with any deletion based on factors such as legal and contractual obligations (such as registry requirements); statutes of limitations; and other legal, business and financial considerations of Misk.
Rights, Options and Inquiries
If the GDPR governs our relationship with you, you have the right to:
obtain access to your personal data and information about the processing thereof;
ask for incorrect, inaccurate or incomplete personal data to be corrected;
request that personal data be erased when it’s no longer needed or if processing it is unlawful;
object to the processing of personal data for marketing purposes or on grounds relating to your particular situation;
request the restriction of the processing of your personal data in specific cases; and
receive your personal data in a machine-readable format and send it to another controller (“data portability”);
withdraw consent to processing of your personal data at any time; provided that, in such case, we may not be able to continue to provide the Products to you;
lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.
If your Personal Data changes, or if you no longer desire our Products, you may correct, update, or deactivate it through your Misk.com Control Panel or by emailing our Customer Support Team at support@misk.com.
You may ask for a list of third parties who provide Products through us by sending an email containing your Misk username and the Products you have purchased to: privacy@misk.com.
Contact By Email
privacy@misk.com
Contact By Mail
Misk.com, Inc.
113 Cherry St #33544
Seattle, WA 98104-2205
